Finding Aid for the Colman Andrews Papers LSC.1428
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings by Colman Andrews
  - Magazine clippings
    - LA mag, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Los Angeles, 1976 October-1983 December (Box 2, Folder 36)
      Copies of clippings
    - Apartment life, 1978 October-1981 January (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Special Cases, 1981 November (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Houston City Magazine, p. 85-86
    - Playgirl, 1978 August-? (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - West, 1986 October 5-1984 June 3 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Telegraph Sunday magazine, 1977 December 4-? (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Radio times (London), 1976 May 8-1980 July 26 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Clippings and copies of clippings
    - D Magazine, 1981 August-1983 March (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - GQ, 1976 May (Box 2, Folder 44)
      p. 92-94
    - New York, 1979 September 17 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      p. 3-4, 62-63
    - Oregon magazine, 1981 April-1981 December (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - New tycoons at the top in Hollywood (The), 1979 Autumn (Box 2, Folder 47)
      MEN (Hong Kong), p. 39-46
    - Catering to Beverly Hills, 1980 September-1980 October (Box 2, Folder 48)
      COOK'S Magazine (The), p. 25-30
    - Three reasons why I hate being a restaurant critic, 1988 November (Box 2, Folder 49)
      Diablo, p. 43-44
    - A food critic looks at seafood in the American restaurant, 1985 Summer (Box 2, Folder 50)
      Seafood leader, p. 63-70
    - Wolfgang Puck, 1987 April (Box 2, Folder 51)
      Face to face/cuisine, p. 92, copy of clipping
    - TWA ambassador, 1983 August-1986 January (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Travel & leisure, 1985 January-1987 April (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Foreign money game (The), 1975 May-1975 June (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Mankind, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - New West, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - New West, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - New West, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - New West, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Guide to Gallic Gastronomy in the Golden State, 1979 December 17 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      New West California French, p. 79-102, 3 copies
    - Metropolitan Home, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Metropolitan Home, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Coast (S.F. only), 1972 March (Box 3, Folder 25)
      p. 61-62
  - Music - biography
    - Duke Ellington, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
      By Don George in collaboration with Colman Andrews
    - Sandy Denny and Marian Segal, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bobby Scott, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Macondo, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Elvin Jones, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ronnie Foster, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Annette Peacock, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Marian Segal, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Leo Kottke, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Horace Silver, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Jazz newcomers, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Black Oak Arkansas, 1972 February 10 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Cannonball Adderly, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Bobby Hutcherson, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Uncle Charlie and his Dog Teddy The Nitty Gritty Band, 1970 November (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Ike and Tina Turner, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Ike Turner, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - The best of Herbie Hancock, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Herbie Hancock interview, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Ian Anderson, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Kenny Rankin, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Jeanne Moreau, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Etta James, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bobby Womack, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Bobby Womack ad, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - I believe in Beatles, 1971 January 4 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Richard Thompson, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Untitled - Z.Z. Hill, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Godfrey Daniel a mystery group - even to their record company, 1972 March 24 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Godfrey Daniel cover art stirs controversy, 1972 April 6 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Lee Morgan shot, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Untitled - Jennifer Warren, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Bill Withers bio, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Ned Doheny bio, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Karla Bonoff, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Leon Ware, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Larry Coryell and Philip Catherine, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Angelo, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Gene Harris biography, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Ian Matthews, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - King Curtis, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Daniel Humair, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Olivia Newton-John, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Savoy jazz shuffle (The), undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Nana Mouskouri, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Joe Pass, 1979 September 17 (Box 4, Folder 50)
      New York
    - Valerie Carter, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Biography from Columbia Records
    - Bill Withers, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Ned Doheny, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Mary Kay Place, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Weather Report, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Donald Byrd: the professor of jazz, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
      Astral weeks
  - Music - live performance reviews
    - Live performance reviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Peter Yarrow and Lazarus at the Troubadour, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Bill Withers and Billy Joel at the Troubadour, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Randy Newman and Jennifer at the Troubadour, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Randy Newman and Ian Matthews at the Troubadour, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Betty Rhodes at the etc., undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Staple Sisters, Robinson Family Plan, and Sea and the East Utopian Mission, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
      At the Lindle Theatre
    - Impulse jazz show: John Klemmer, Archia Shepp, Mike White, and Alice Coltrane, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      At the Santa Monica civic auditorium
    - Gladys Knight and the Pips at the Climax II, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Dr. Hook and the Medicine Show and Ballin' Jack (Troubadour), February 6 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - J.J. Cale and Bonnie Raitt at the Ash Grove, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Mike Clifford and Kay Dennis at Ye Little Club, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Leo Kottke and England Dan and John Ford Coley at the Troubadour, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Nana Mouskouri at the Dorothy Chandler Pavilion, March 6 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Two evenings at Shelley's Manne*hole, February 16-17 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Teddy Edwards and Thelonius Monk
    - Persuasions, Johnny Otis Show, and Cheech & Chong, February 5 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      At the Santa Monica Civic Auditorium
    - Rita Coolidge and Crazy Horse at the Troubadour, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Jazz at the Whisky a go go: The Mahavishnu Orchestra with John McLaughlin, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
      And the Herbie Hancock Sextet
    - French concert, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Mahavishnu Orchestra with John McLaughlin at the Whiskey, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Donny Hathaway "live" - 30-second spot #1-3, undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Low marks of well-heeled boys (The), undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Home grown jazz in Romania, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Monday night at Reykjavik, undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Jazz in Belgrade, undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Rockin' in Reykjavik or No manna is in Iceland, undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Pioneers, fifties, light music, jazz, rock, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Ray Charles at the Opera, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Angela in Paris, 1971 October 4 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Blowing a haif amp fuse; Angela Davis Day in New York, 1971 September 25 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Ron Carter, Sonny Rollins and McCoy Tyner, with Al Foster, 1978 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Milan jazz festival, undated (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Music - record labels
    - Blue note, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Record reviews
    - A Testament to the blues, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Love records, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fantasy records, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Music - record reviews
    - Miscellaneous album and record reviews, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Circular, 1973 August 20-1974 November 11 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Jazz record and album briefs, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - King heroin by James Brown, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Music by Charlie Mingus, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Wilderness road, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Choma (Burn) by Harold Land, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Communication by Bobby Womack, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stories by David Blue, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lubbock (on everything) by Terry Allen, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Exile on main street, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Harvest by Neil Young, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Savoy reissues, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Jazz Magazine
    - Apogee by Pete Christlieb/Warn Marsh Quintet, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Enchance by Billy Hart, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Excitable boy by Warren Zevon, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Music for 18 musicians by Steve Reich, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Gone by Jerry Williams, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Sojourn by Mickey Tucker, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Vladimir Vlasov: concerto no. 1; Henri Sauguet: Melodie Concertante, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - I'm ready by Muddy Waters, undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Groovy situation (A) by Reuben Wilson, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Henry the human fly by Richard Thompson, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Bundle of joy by Freddie Hubbard and Knucklebean by Bobby Hutcherson, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Spotlight kid (The) by Captain Beefheart, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - New directions by Jack DeJohnette, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Philip Catherine, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Jazz column, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Poetry
    - Letter to someone I used to know, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ansedonia - What I did this summer, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Flight of the 509 (The), undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - St. Clement of the whales, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Four postcards from Italy, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Wolves (The), undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Jill, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Poems with a contemporaneous bent, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Miracle (The), undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Westward, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Capodanno, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - A few words on the tribes of Persia, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Nursery rhyme, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Book-Casemates (The), undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Poetry book reviews, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Poetry review (Snow), undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Poetry reviews (Amis, Silk, Vliet, Poetry East), undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Restaurant reviews
    - Southwestern food/coyote café, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - London restaurants, undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - New southern cooking, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Qs mbj piece, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Costa Brava restaurants, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Milan restaurants -- revised, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - New Year's bit -- by phone to LAT, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Restaurants/where to go next, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - East-West eats, undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Jimmy's, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Mee krob hunters (The), undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Valentine's day special, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Butterfield, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 60 Oui restaurants, 1976 August (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Maxim's, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - American restaurants of Paris (The), undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Great French restaurants of the United States, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Restaurant listing for New West, 1981 February 4 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Overgrown gourmet and New York layabout's guide (The), Fall 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Two Russian restaurants, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
      2 drafts
    - World trade center restaurants, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Vienna hofbrau, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Taming of the stew (The), undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Haremburger, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Musso and Frank's grill, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Adriatic (The), undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Mouling and Lucky restaurant, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Paris restaurant -- Duquesnoy, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - To dull the bite of it, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Napa Valley inns and restaurants, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Ice cream best bet, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - California critic, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Notes for ma maison newsletter, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Never used
    - Ma Maison II; the sequel, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Café Via Veneto, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - La famiglia, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Gio's, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Siamese princess, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Bagatelle, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Betsy (The) -- notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Other place update (The), 1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - La petite chaya, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Tasca/from Spain, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - River café, undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Auberge des Deux Signes (Paris), undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Spago, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Chez Panisse party, undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Metro -- Chez Panisse 15th anniversary, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Seasons, undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Rex fish dinner, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Jams, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Out of a jams, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Au Chambertin -- Santa Barbara, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Le Cherche-midi -- revised, undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - La Cagouille, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Hostellerie du Vieux Moulin, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Guy Savoy review, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Guy Savoy/l' ambroisie, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Akbar/kapoor story, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - El Encanto (Santa Barbara), undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Wolfgang Puck/"L.A. look" restaurants, undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Le Tre Vaselle, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Jamdani/zen central, undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - River café (The), (London), undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Cucina rustica, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - An American place//frozen food lunch, undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - An American place, undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Campton place restaurant (San Francisco), undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Chez Gu, undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous restaurant reviews, undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Manufacture, undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
      To Stanley Dry -- food & wine editorial
    - Le St. Michel, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Orient Express, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Aegean Isles/chowder call, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Maximin, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
      To Cathryn Bradbury -- domino
    - Sticky fingers (secrets), undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Stucki/restaurant bruderholz, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Restaurant du Port de Peche (Casablanca), undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Three casual French restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
      To Ruth Reichl
    - Eccentric (The), undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Eldorado Petit -- is this the best restaurant in the world?, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Le Grand Louvre, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - La Baita mushroom restaurant, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - China grill -- secrets of the city, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Maison Blanche, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
      To Mary Beth Jordan
    - BWY cafes, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Caribbean terrace, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Le Cherche Midi, 1983 September (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Aegean Isles at (islands?) the Marina Chowder Grill, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Palm Court (The), undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - New Los Angeles restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - New Los Angeles restaurants (campanile & patina), undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
      To Mr. Stanley Dry -- food & wine magazine editorial
    - Los Angeles restaurant guide, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Los Angeles -- restaurant secrets of the city, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Los Angeles restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
      4 drafts, 1 addition
    - Quintessential L.A. restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Los Angeles restaurant neighborhoods, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Includes revised draft
    - L.A. restaurant secrets, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Los Angeles restaurant business, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Thai restaurants in Los Angeles, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Santa Barbara -- by phone to MH, 1983 August 18 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Santa Barbara restaurant briefs, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Santa Barbara restaurant update (Olive Mill Bistro and El Encanto), undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - California cuisine, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
      Book proposal
    - Belgian restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
      Parts one, two, and three
    - French restaurant guides, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - French restaurant guide, undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Notes towards a Paris restaurant guide, undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - New Paris bistros, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Paris restaurant update, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Paris restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Paris bistros, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
      To Ruth Reichl/Laurie Ochoa
    - Paris restaurants #1 (Gerard Pangaud) and #2 (Guy Savoy), undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Verona restaurants #1 and #2, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Kansas City restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Washington state restaurants -- revised, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Florence restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Florence restaurants (The right place), undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Restaurants of Provence, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Orson Welles on Hollywood restaurants, etc., undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Santa Maria barbecue, undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Trouble with New York restaurants (The), undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
      3 copies
    - New York American restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - New York restaurants, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - New York restaurant story add (Physicians lifestyle), undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - New York food in Los Angeles -- bites of the big apple, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - New York bistros and trattorias, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - American restaurants in Paris, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Seattle restaurants, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Parts one and two
    - Chicago restaurants (Or, the eccentric, etc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Nice, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Washington D.C. restaurants -- the new administration, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Boston restaurants (Lydia Shire), undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Dining in East Berlin, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
      To Leslie Ward, travel section
    - Budapest coffee houses, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Minneapolis restaurants, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Barcelona, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Barcelona restaurants, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Serious eater's guide to Barcelona (A) -- revised, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Catalan cuisine -- the 650-year-old next big thing, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Catalan cuisine -- revised, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
      To Julie Mautner
    - Legends and curiosities of Catalan cuisine, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - AIWF conference/Catalan cuisine, 1988 April (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 1989 Guide Michelin, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Met grill -- lopata/tihany, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Tristan, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - L' Auberge du Pere Bise, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Azzurro, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Mr. Food, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Six restaurants worth driving an hour for (more or less), undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Gitanjali, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Restaurant notes for LA weekly, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Le Dome, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - L' Orangerie, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Regional Italian cooking; upscale Palio and Harry, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Reel Inn (The), undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Friday restaurant column, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Roundabout - restaurant reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - You - restaurant reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - L.A. Times, undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Hot props, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Restaurant reviews [various restaurants], undated; [2 folders.] (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Best restaurants - Southern California, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant column, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Restaurant notebook, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Restaurant notebook, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant notebook, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Restaurant notebook, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Restaurant notebook, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Restaurant notebook, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Restaurant reviews - book
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
      Introduction, biography, notes
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
      A
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
      B
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
      C
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
      D
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
      E
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
      F
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
      G
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
      H
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
      I
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
      J
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
      K
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
      L
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
      M
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
      N
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
      O
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
      P-Q
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
      R
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
      S
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
      T
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
      U
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
      V
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
      W-X
    - Best restaurants/Los Angeles, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Y-Z
  - Stories/screenplays
    - Diffa showhouse, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Travelogue (The), undated (Box 22, Folder 2)